我和我的兄弟姐妹
My siblings and I
是历史上最古老的吸血鬼
are the first vampires in all of history,
也就是始祖家族
The Originals.
和他们不同的是 我是一个混血儿...一半吸血鬼 一半狼人
Unlike them, I am a hybrid...half vampire, half werewolf.
本视频由 时光机字幕组 制作发布
字幕仅限学习  严禁用于任何商业行为
三百年前 我们帮助创建了新奥尔良
300 years ago,we helped build New Orleans.
现在 一群女巫们引诱我们重返这里
Now we've returned, drawn back by a coven of witches
翻译:  Harriet 纪晓芙 李铭烟 岁寒缺松 小雪 张无忌
她们威胁怀了我孩子的女人
who threaten the woman carrying my child.
那个婴儿会害死我们所有人
That baby will bring death to us all.
校对:  范遥 纪晓芙 张无忌
我的哥哥Elijah和他们交涉过
My brother Elijah dealt with them.
没人伤害我的家人后还能活着
No one hurts my family and lives.
时间轴:  Jer-Knigんt
我们认为Hayley会平安无事
We thought Hayley would be safe.
我是Marcel
I'm Marcel.
我不觉得我们见过面
I don't think we've met.
监制:  杨逍
Hayley不见了 她去哪儿了？
Hayley is gone. Where is she?
什么？
What?
Marcel来过
Marcel was here.
但我们错了
We were wrong.
女士们 先生们
Ladies, gentlemen,
欢迎参加格斗之夜...
welcome to fight night...
格斗之夜的首要规则就是
And the first rule of fight night is,
今夜过后还没倒下的吸血鬼
the vampire left standing at the end of the night
会离核心集团和一枚日光戒指...
is one step closer to the inner circle
更近一步
and one of these...a daylight ring.
如果你那小小的暴力行径能让我印象深刻的话
If you can impress me with a little ultra-violence,
你也可以享受到阳光洒在脸上的温暖
you too can enjoy the warmth of the sun on your face.
你只需要拿出真本事来
All you got to do is kick a little ass.
我们开始吧
So here we go.
欢迎我们的第一对竞争者...
Our first two contenders...
Felicia和Otto
Felicia and Otto.
呼！该死的 小妞 挺厉害嘛
Whoo! Damn, girl, not bad.
晚上好 我想说几句
Good evening. I'd like a word.
你来这里干什么？
What do you think you're doing?
似乎我们打扰了
It appears that we've interrupted
一群脏兮兮的业余拳击手
a collection of filthy amateurs.
我们来这里找那个女孩子
We've come here for the girl.
把她交给我们 否则...我们会杀得这里片甲不留
Give her to us,or...We kill everyone here.
先拿你开刀
starting with you
你们两个神经病
You two got a lot of nerve
闯进我的家里 要东要西的
coming into my home and making demands.
你家 呵呵？
Your home, is it?
我们要那个女孩 别让我再说一遍
The girl. I will not ask again.
我猜你们指的是Hayley...
I assume you're talking about Hayley...
这么高 深色头发 态度死贱
yay high, dark hair, bitchy attitude.
她到底是谁？
Who is she, anyway?
一位老朋友
She's an old friend.
你知道我对老朋友的感情有多深
You know how sentimental I am about old friends.
好吧 她不在我这
Well, I ain't got her,
你们先别忙着唠叨
and before you start whining,
昨天晚上我的确拜访过她
I did pay her a little visit last night.
因为突然有点怀旧
I was feeling nostalgic.
所以我回了一趟
So I took a trip out to the plantation
我曾做过奴隶的种植园
where I used to be a slave,
当我发现
and imagine my surprise when I realized
吸血鬼始祖家族竟然住在那里
that the original family of vampires
我简直惊呆了
had taken up residence.
你家Hayley开了门
Your girl Hayley answered the door.
我们相互问候了一下 就这样
We exchanged hellos.That was it.
如果你不相信我 你可以自己找
You don't believe me, look around.
见鬼 我甚至还会帮你们找到她
Hell, I'll even help you find her,
但我想问的是
but the question I'd ask is,
如果Hayley不在这里
if Hayley isn't here,
那她能去哪里呢？
then where is she?
开玩笑吧？
Seriously?
Tyler?
Hayley 你不会想跟我打上一架的
You don't want to fight me, Hayley.
你知道你赢不了一个混血儿的
You know you can't beat a hybrid.
啊！放我走
Aah! Let me go,
你这个暗箭伤人的混血杂种  一坨...
you backstabbing, half-breed piece of sh...
你丫闭嘴！
shut up!
始祖家族
第一季第七集
也就是一帮乌合之众
Not the most attractive community,
你觉得呢？
are they?
你知道他们能听见你说的话
You do realize they can hear you.
你知道我根本不会在乎
You do realize I don't care.
Elijah 我还是更喜欢待在棺材里的你
You know, Elijah, I liked you better in that box,
但是 Klaus 我的恩师 我亏欠你太多
but, Klaus, my sire, you I owe the world,
而且我向来尊师敬道
and I always show respect to my elders.
如果你的特殊女友失踪了
If your special lady friend is missing,
可以让女巫来帮你们
you can benefit from the help of a witch,
既然我掌控着这个城市的女巫们
and since I control all the witches in this town,
我允许你们用一个小小的定位咒
I'll Grant you one little locator spell.
Sabine是法语区最好的导游
Sabine is the best guide in the quarter.
如果你们想找到什么人
You need to find someone,
我保证她可以帮到你们
I guarantee she's your girl.
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
我讨厌长话短说 但太阳很快就要升起
I hate to cut this short, but the sun is coming up soon.
我的夜行者们必须得进屋里
My nightwalkers need to get inside,
而且还有一个城市要打理
and I've got a city to run.
我就不陪你们寻找迷途羔羊了
I'll leave you to track down your lost sheep.
你能找到她吗？
Can you find her?
我尽量
I can try.
这是什么地方？
What is this place?
路易斯安那的一个小旮旯
The armpit of Louisiana.
你拿着刀想干嘛？
What are you gonna do with that?
这取决于你
Depends on you.
嘿 是你攻击我的 还记得吗？
Hey, you attacked me, remember?
你在我家后院伏击了我
You ambushed me in my own back yard.
那不是你家的后院 那是Klaus家的后院
It's not your back yard.It's Klaus'.
你和那个神经病住在一个宅邸里
You're shacked up in a mansion with that psycho,
已经不再是我在阿巴拉契亚山脉遇到的那个
a long way from the girl I met in the appalachians
帮助过很多狼人的女孩子
helping other werewolves.
Tyler 对不起 自从最后一次见到你之后
Tyler, I'm sorry, but a lot has happened
发生了很多事情
since the last time I saw you.
你想说的是你怎么怀孕的？
You mean like how you're pregnant?
一个神奇混血宝宝 没错 我都知道了
A hybrid baby. Yeah. I know all about it.
我一直行走于河口一带
I've been roaming around the bayou
打探各种消息
asking questions.
我来告诉你我都打听到了什么
Let me tell you what I learned.
这个月牙状胎记意味着
This crescent birthmark means you come
你来自大家族 对这个地区的狼人而言
from a big shot family, some kind of royalty
你的家族就是王族
to the werewolves of this region,
就在这里
and right here,
这儿就是那个家族的遗迹了
this is all that's left of them.
嘿 救救我
Hey, help me.
他们救不了你
They can't help you.
他们躲在丛林里
They're in the woods hiding
因为数十年来
because they've been persecuted
他们被吸血鬼所迫害
for decades by vampires.
是她吗？
Is that her?
是的 Dwayne 把她带进去
Yeah, Dwayne. Get her inside.
Tyler?
她在荒郊野外
She's in the back country,
从霍马向里一直走到河口深处
way out past houma, deep in the bayou.
我也没指望你能查得更具体
I don't suppose you could be more precise.
怎么了 Elijah
What's the matter, Elijah,
你在担心沼泽地的泥
are you worried a bit suppose of splashing about in the bog
会毁了你昂贵的鞋子吗？
might ruin your expensive shoes?
事实上 前阵子被监禁这么久
As a matter of fact, after my recent confinement,
我需要在乡间优雅的散个步
I could use a decent stroll through the countryside.
营地那里流传着
There are stories of exiled werewolves,
被驱逐的狼族的故事
encampments.
如果Hayley真的走那么远
If Hayley went out that far,
有可能 她去找他们了
chances are, she went to find them.
显而易见 她一直希望结识
Clearly, she hopes to make the acquaintance
狼人族群
of more like herself.
我猜是我们家对她照顾的不够好
I suppose our company wasn't good enough for her.
你也可以随时加入他们 你懂的
You could always join them, you know.
呃 饮酒游戏
Uh, drinking games.
这不是我的菜
It's not really my thing.
总让我想起高中时候的恶棍
It kind of reminds me of the jocks in my High School.
那会儿太多人喜欢拿管子灌人鼻子
We had a pretty high quota of what you'd call
就是你们说的鼻冲洗嘴管
douche nozzles.
-恶霸 哈？ -是啊
Bullies, huh? Yeah.
真想瞧瞧你现在看到那些家伙会怎么样
Wonder what'd happen if you saw those guys now.
我打赌你会把他们撕碎 对吧？
I bet you'd tear them apart, right?
是啊 完全如此
Ah, yeah, totally.
哈 可能会像吸血鬼忍者那样
Ha! Probably go all vamp ninja on them.
哈哈哈 Josh你真是一个有趣的人
Ha ha ha! You're a funny guy, Josh.
实际上 我觉得昨晚
In fact, I thought it was really
真的很有趣 你知道吗
funny last night, you know,
看到你出现在
seeing you at that plantation
Klaus住的种植园
where Klaus is staying.
哦吼 哇哈哈！
Ho ho! Ha ha ha!
Josh 要去哪么？
You going somewhere, Josh?
我们应该朝向水流走 往南去
We should head south towards the water.
你决心要找到小狼妞啊
You seem quite determined to find the little wolf.
Niklaus 如果你嫌我行动太快的话
If I'm moving too fast for you, Niklaus,
大可以在车里等着
you're welcome to wait in the car.
不过要确保把车窗都摇下来
Do be certain to leave the windows down.
啊 看来我提到敏感话题了
Ah, so I've touched a nerve.
你已经开始爱慕这个女孩了
You've begun to admire this girl.
也许这就是为什么从你回来起
Perhaps that's why you've been barking orders
一直发号施令
since your return, hoping to impress Hayley
就为了给Hayley留下好印象
by assuming the role of family patriarch.
如果你坚持把她当作
You want to insist on treating her
一个会行走的恒温箱
like a walking incubator,
那你就错了
then that's your mistake.
你闻到她的气味了吗？
Have you found her scent?
没有
No...
但我闻到了其他人的
But I found someone else's.
这辆车散发着他的臭味
This vehicle reeks
我以为已经摆脱了他
of someone I thought I was rid of...
Tyler Lockwood
Tyler Lockwood.
为什么你那个神秘瀑布镇的混血小伙伴
And why would your little hybrid sidekick
会对Hayley感兴趣呢？
from Mystic Falls have any interest in Hayley?
因为我追求过他的女朋友 而他想报仇
He wants revenge because I went after his girl.
为什么我觉得这是你最不起眼的错误呢？
Why do I suspect this is the least of your offenses?
在我有办法让混血认祖归宗的时候
Back when I had the means to sire hybrids,
他是我第一个混血
he was my first,
虽然在这件事上我没有给他多少选择
although I didn't give him much choice in the matter.
他一开始很忠诚
He was loyal in the beginning,
但后来越来越不听话
but he grew insubordinate,
还让其他混血都和我作对
turned my other hybrids against me.
我不能容忍
I couldn't have that.
所以我把他们都杀了
So I massacred the lot of them.
在我要了结他之前
Tyler ran like a coward
Tyler像懦夫一样跑了
before I could finish him off.
你还有其他什么要分享的吗？
Anything else that you would like to share?
那个 还有他妈妈的事
Well, there was this business with his mum.
你杀了他妈妈 真棒
You killed his mother.Wonderful.
是他需要得到教训啊
He needed to be taught a lesson.
那你要得到什么教训呢 Niklaus
And what lesson will you be taught, Niklaus,
如果他为了报复你而伤害Hayley呢？
if he retaliates by harming Hayley?
所以你的确喜欢她 好吧 那你去啊
So you do care about her. Well, go on, then.
去吧 哥哥 去救她
Have at it, brother. Save her.
我看你能把她宠成什么样
Claim what spoils you can.
她的一切我早就尝过鲜了
I've sampled what she has to offer,
还有 让我告诉你 她可是妙不可言呢
and, let me tell you, she is exquisite.
Niklaus 帮我...
Niklaus, so help me...
够了
enough.
我会亲手杀了Tyler Lockwood
I'll kill Tyler Lockwood myself.
Marcel 有情况
Marcel, something is happening.
法语区有女巫在施法
There's a witch doing magic in the quarter.
不用担心 那个是经我认可的
Oh, no worries. That one is Marcel-approved.
-另外... -哦！
Besides...Oh!
你得处理另外一件事
Got something else for you to handle.
哦天呐 你是那个超级女巫
Oh, no. You're the super witch.
和Josh打个招呼
Say hi to Josh.
你把他带来干嘛？
Why would you bring him here?
Josh有麻烦了
Josh has a problem.
Klaus控制他来监视我
Klaus compelled him to spy on me.
啊！
Agh!
我绝对不允许
I can't have that.
所以我想 杀了Josh就行
So I thought,"I'll just kill Josh."
Marcel 求你了 这不是我的错
Marcel, please. It's not my fault.
但我又想到 杀掉一个吸血鬼
Then I thought,"killing a vampire,
就会违反我自己的规则
that would be breaking my own rule."
所以聪明的做法就是给Josh洗脑
Smart thing to do is to flip Josh.
这样他就可以告诉Klaus我想让他说的一切
That way, he can tell Klaus whatever I want.
他甚至可以帮我监视Klaus
He could even spy for me.
我们要做的就是解除Klaus的意念操纵
All we got to do is wipe away that compulsion.
你觉得怎么样？
So what do you think?
我可以让他忘了Klaus告诉他的事情
I can make him forget what Klaus told him,
但Klaus命令的越多
but the more Klaus said,
就会疼得越厉害
the more it's gonna hurt.
嗯...那可能会很疼呢
Hmm, probably gonna hurt a lot.
Josh？
我会配合的
I'll do it,
随便怎样都行
anything, yes.
我们说的痛苦到底是什么程度呢？
How much pain are we talking?
Tyler 最近一直有只狼在盯着我
Tyler, there's been a wolf watching me lately.
就像它本来就知道我是他们中的一员似的保护我
Protecting me like it instinctively knows that I'm part of its pack.
你是混血儿 你可以随时变成狼人
You're a hybrid. You can turn into a wolf whenever you want.
那是你么？
Was it you?
不是
No.
但你说的对
But you're right.
只有混血儿才能控制自己在何时变身
Only hybrids can control when they change.
我是除了Klaus之外唯一剩下的混血儿了
And I'm the only one left besides Klaus,
这就是我们在这里的原因
which is why we're here.
不管你怎么想 怎么做
Whatever you think you're doing, you know,
整个始祖家族已经达成某种协议
get a whole original family has made some sort of pack
来保护我和我的孩子平安无事
or something to keep me and the baby safe.
如果你伤害我 他们会杀了你的
So if you hurt me, they'll kill you.
是什么让你觉得我会怕死呢
What makes you think I'm afraid to die.
准备好了么？
you're ready for this?
动手吧
let's do it.
你要干什么？
What are you doing?
Tyler 求你了 别 Tyler！
Tyler, please, no, Tyler!
Klaus 毁了我生命里所有美好的东西
Klaus destroyed everything good in my life.
所以我要夺走他最想要的
So I'm gonna take away the thing he wants most.
不要 求你了 Tyler 不要这样
No, please, Tyler, please.
我以为你走了 离不开家是吗？
I thought you were leaving town. Couldn't stay away, huh?
我本来已经过了半个路易斯安那州了
I was half past Louisiana when I found out
结果我发现你入侵了我家
you invaded our home.
你对Hayley做了什么？
What have you done with Hayley?
你生气的时候真性感
You're so hot when you're angry.
啊！
Uh!
你利用了我
You used me.
我很肯定这是相互的
I'm pretty sure that was mutual.
被你迷昏了头 我像傻子一样和你睡了
Beguiled by your charms, I slept with you like a fool,
把你带到我家 然后你就抓走了Hayley
led you to our home, and then you took Hayley.
哇哦 我谁都没抓
Whoa, I didn't take anybody.
我已经和你的哥哥们弄清这件事了
I already sorted this out with your brothers,
别回避问题
but it begs the question,
你为什么回来？
why'd you come back?
如果Klaus知道你找到去种植园的路
If Klaus learns it's my fault
是因为我的过失...
you found your way to the plantation...
你真的认为我会出卖你吗？
you really think I'd rat you out?
拜托
Come on.
如果你真的认为在一千年中我做出过
If you think that I'd ever in 1,000 years
任何伤害你的事
do anything to hurt you,
你就把我错当成Klaus了
you got me confused with Klaus.
你所有的魅力和挑逗
All your charmsand flirtations
仅仅证明你和Klaus一样
simply prove you're every bit the liar
是个不折不扣的骗子和操控者
and manipulator that Klaus is.
你真是这么想的吗？
Is that what you really think?
那就想尽办法证明我错了
By all means, prove me wrong.
好吧 跟我来
Fine. Come on.
有些东西要你看
Something you need to see.
别用这种评判的眼光
Don't get all judgey.
Dwayne知道他在做什么
Dwayne knew what he was getting into.
他是自愿的
He volunteered.
自愿让你杀了他？
For you to kill him?
他是狼人 死的时候体内有你的血
Dwayne is a werewolf who died with your blood in his system,
和你的混血孩子一样的血
same blood you share with your hybrid baby.
你在试着把他变成个混血
You're trying to turn him into a hybrid.
那是不可能的
That's impossible.
我一直和全国的狼群打交道
Been running with wolf packs all over the country.
和其中一个女巫联系很紧密
One of them was tight with a witch.
她对你的宝宝有噩梦般的预见
She had nightmare visions about your baby
Klaus会用他的血
and how Klaus could use its blood
来建造一支混血奴隶军团
to make an army of hybrid slaves.
我对这些女巫
I am sick of these witches
和她们对我孩子的预见感到恶心
and the premonitions about my baby.
它只是一个孩子
It's just a baby.
也许是 也许不是
Maybe. Maybe not.
这就是为什么Dwayne要来这
That's where Dwayne comes in.
你看 他很乐意成为试验对象
You see, he was happy to be the test case.
如果你还没注意到 这些人
If you haven't noticed, these people
活着没什么盼头
don't have much to live for.
他们都期待成为
They'd all welcome the chance to become
更优良的物种
the superior species.
问题是 所有的混血都对Klaus认祖归宗
Trouble is, all hybrids are sired to Klaus.
他们对他言听计从
They follow his every move.
我不会让这一切发生的
No way I'd let that happen.
你怎么就这么确定Klaus知道
How can you be so sure Klaus knows
这孩子的血能做什么？
what the baby's blood will do?
你怎么想的？
What do you think?
Klaus Mikaelson..
Klaus Mikaelson...
他杀过无数男人 女人 还有小狗之类的生灵
killer of men, women, and puppies...
却突然间想做父亲了
all of a sudden wants to be a daddy,
或者说他根本就另有不可告人的目的
or he's got an ulterior motive.
混血可以在阳光下行走
Hybrids can walk in the sun.
他们的咬伤对吸血鬼来说是致命的
Their bite is lethal to vampires.
一个星期他们就能掌控整个新奥尔良
They'll take over New Orleans by the end of the week,
而你知道怎样才能阻止Klaus吗？
and you know what's gonna stop Klaus then?
怎样都不能
Nothing.
你必须得吸她的血
You're gonna have to feed on her.
什么？不
What? No.
啊..
Aah...
动手啊
do it.
不！不！啊！
No. No! Aah!
Dwayne…放松
Dwayne... easy.
看着我 看着我
Look at me. Look at me.
你没事了
You're ok.
我不是没事 是好极了
I'm better than ok.
我很抱歉 但是你这样只会更糟
I'm sorry, but it's just gonna get worse.
Klaus的催眠太深了
Klaus' compulsion runs deep.
你需要想点别的
You need to think of something else,
别再想这些了
take your mind off it.
你喜欢音乐吗？
Do you like music?
什么？什么？
What? What?
我现在没心思想音乐
I can't think about music right now.
为什么？我不明白
Why? I don't know.
可能因为你在用巫毒给我洗脑
Maybe because you're giving me a voodoo lobotomy.
你喜欢爵士乐吗？
Do you like jazz?
唉...
Oh...
那你喜欢什么？
So what, then?
俱乐部里的东西吧...
Club stuff...
大房间 迷幻舞曲 你懂的...
house, trance, you know...
嗯呲嗒呲……
nn ss nn ss nn ss
我是女巫 又不是阿米什人
I'm a witch. I'm not amish.
因为我才十六岁 不去俱乐部的
It's just I'm only 16. I don't go to clubs.
我十六岁的时候早就混迹各种俱乐部了
When I was 16, I'd been to like, 100 clubs.
天呐 才过去四年
God, it was only 4 years ago.
感觉却像是上辈子
Feels like another life.
我当时只是想多见一些男孩
All I wanted to do was meet boys.
可这一切却复杂多了
Things are so much more complicated.
现在我还是想见男孩
I mean, now all I want to do is meet boys
但是为了吸他们的血
and feed on people's blood,
得到一个日光戒
get one of those daylight rings
那样我就不会在阳光下烧死
so I don't burn in the sunlight,
就能像个普通人一样
all perfectly normal things.
我爱古典音乐...
I like the classics...
波切尼 巴赫 莫扎特
puccini, bach, Mozart.
我练过钢琴
I took piano,
但我困在这里 没有机会弹琴了
not that it matters while I'm stuck here.
为什么不弹？
Why not?
Marcel担心有人会听见
Marcel is worried that someone could hear.
这不怪他
It's not his fault.
他只是想保护我
He just wants to keep me safe.
保护你什么？
Safe from what?
大体来说 就是一帮疯狂的女巫们
Basically, a coven of psycho witches
想在血祭仪式上杀掉我
want to sacrifice me in a blood ritual.
噢 哇噢 好吧
Oh, wow. Ok.
啊...很抱歉...
Uh, I'm...Sorry.
别担心 我会把她们一网打尽
Don't be. I'm gonna destroy them all,
等到她们都消失了
and once they're gone,
一切又会回到正轨
everything will go back to normal.
我会继续我原来的生活
I'll have my old life back.
成功了 对不对？他是个混血了
It worked, didn't it? He's a hybrid.
如果你落到Klaus手里
If Klaus gets a hold of you,
如果他掌控着这个孩子 他就赢了
if he gets that kid, he wins.
那就帮我把孩子藏起来
Then help me hide the baby from him.
帮我逃走
Help me run.
他会找到你的
He'll find you.
他会带走你的孩子
He'll take your kid away,
他会制造更多的混血怪物
and he'll make more hybrid monsters,
一帮完全听命于他的奴隶
slaves who do everything he says.
Tyler 无论你想要做什么
Tyler, whatever you're thinking of doing,
一定还有其他办法的
there has to be another way.
你不是这样的人
You're not like this.
啊！这样很蠢！
Agh! That was stupid.
离她远点
Get away from her.
关你屁事？
What do you care?
我说了 走开
I said, get away.
你已经得到你想要的 滚开
You got what you wanted. Now get lost.
Dwayne 他要杀了我
Dwayne, he's gonna kill me.
他还要杀了你
He's gonna kill you, too.
他说混血儿活着
He said that hybrids
太危险了
are too dangerous to live.
你必须阻止他
You need to stop him.
闭嘴！哦！
Shut up. Uh!
原谅我
Forgive me.
还以为你有危险
Thought you were in danger.
看来我错了
It appears I was mistaken.
你绝对想不到我今天有多衰
You will not believe the crap day that I'm having.
我带你回家
Let me take you home.
Elijah…
关于这个孩子你还需要多了解一些
There's something you need to know about the baby.
Hayley.
别让这一切变得更加艰难
don't make this harder than it has to be.
放弃吧...
Give up now...
我会很快解决的
I'll end it quick.
说的真好
Quite an offer,
不过我是不会这么跟你说的
though not one I'll be extending to you.
Klaus
嘿 Tyler 你看上去不错
Hello, Tyler.You look well.
不过我打算改变一下
I aim to change that.
威胁一个怀孕的女孩
Threatening a pregnant girl
就为了报复我
in order to exact revenge against me.
我还从没想到过你会堕落至此
I never expected you to sink so low.
我承认 我很有感触
I admit, I'm impressed.
我过去常跟着你混
I used to hang out with you.
不过我想那些事情已经一去不复返了
I guess something must have rubbed off.
你觉得Caroline会怎么想呢
What do you think Caroline would say
如果她看到你变成这样？
if she saw what you've become?
也许在我告知她你死讯的时候
Perhaps I'll ask her when I call her
会顺便问问
to tell her of your demise.
不管我发什么了什么
Whatever happens to me,
Caroline绝对不会停止恨你的
Caroline is never gonna stop hating you.
来吧 伙计 再拼命点
Come on, mate. Give it a bit more effort.
让我玩个痛快
I want to enjoy myself.
这是什么地方？
What is this place?
这是个花园
This is the garden.
是我用来惩罚那些违反我规矩的吸血鬼的地方
It's where I punish vampires who break my rules,
但很久以前 这里有别的用途
but a long time ago, used to be something else.
说说吧 告诉我你看到了什么
Go on. Tell me what you see.
双层结构 希腊式的圆柱
Two stories, Greek columns,
环绕式门廊 高高的天花板
wraparound porch, high ceilings,
还有顶窗
transom windows.
很漂亮 那又怎样？
It's lovely. So what?
这是我为你设计的 原本将是我们的家
So I designed it for you. It was gonna be ours.
那…
That...
这本应该是我们共度美好生活的地方？
this was supposed to be our happily ever after?
你和我的
Yours and mine,
如果你没有跟着Klaus逃走的话
except you flew the coop with Klaus.
我已经为这个地方打好了地基
I already built the foundation for the place.
你离开后就停工了
I halted construction after you took off.
我打算等你回来再继续
Plan was to wait for you to return.
但你没有
You never did.
所以这里成了我埋藏那些背叛我的人的地方
So now it's where I bury the people who betray me.
你那时应该跟我走的
You could've come after me.
你和Klaus在一起 我不知道你在哪
You were with Klaus. I didn't know where.
也不知道你还想不想和我在一起
I didn't know if you still wanted to be with me.
你当时需要做的就是回家
All you had to do was come home.
这比你想的要复杂得多
It was more complicated than that.
我们离开这没多久
Not long after we left here,
他就拿匕首扎进了我的心脏
he put a dagger in my heart
然后把我封在棺材里九十年
and stuck me in a box for 90 years.
他偷走我一个世纪的光阴 好像对他都不算什么
He stole a century from me like it were nothing.
这就是他 Rebekah
That's what he does, Rebekah.
Klaus永远都不会开心的
Klaus will never be happy.
如果有人得到了他得不到的
He'll be damned if he ever lets anyone
他会变得非常凶残
get something that he can't have.
我知道
I know.
我已经跟着他的节奏
I've been dancing to this song
活了一千年
for 1,000 years.
从现在开始 你还有一个选择
Starting right now, you have a choice
在一个随心所欲 任意剥夺你的快乐
between the brother who takes away your happiness
的哥哥和一个想给你
whenever he feels like it and the man who wants
全世界的男人之间做出选择
to give you everything you ever wanted.
他会当着我的面杀了你
He will kill you in front of my eyes
为了泄恨
out of spite.
如果我们先摆脱他就不一定了
Not if we get rid of him first.
Klaus肯定已经知道了
Klaus must have known.
这是唯一的解释
That's the only explanation.
他一点也不在乎这个孩子
He could care less about the baby.
他只是想让孩子生下来
He just wants her to be born
这样他就能制造更多的混血儿
so he can use her to make more sired hybrids.
尽管Dwayne表现出来的
Although the way that Dwayne was acting,
更像是对我认祖归宗了
it was more like he was sired to me.
我应该带你回家
I should take you home.
开什么玩笑？哪里是家？
Are you serious? Home to what?
听着 不管我弟弟的意图如何
Look. Regardless of my brother's intentions,
我始终如一
mine remain the same.
我说过会保护你
I said that I would protect you,
就算是Klaus想伤害你也不行
even, if need be, from Klaus himself.
我可以自己照顾自己
I can take care of myself.
我一直都是靠自己的
I've done it for a long time.
这就是你的复仇计划吗 Tyler？
Is this your idea of revenge, Tyler,
累人的捉迷藏游戏？
grueling game of hide-and-seek?
不如我们来做个了结吧
Let's end this, shall we?
呀！呀！
Raagh! Raagh!
你狗胆包天？
How dare you?
这才刚刚开始
I'm just getting started.
啊！
Aagh!
你已经开始饥渴了
You've grown bloodthirsty.
也许你该庆幸你母亲没有活着
Perhaps it's best your mother didn't live
看到你这个样子
to see you like this.
哈哈哈！
Ha ha ha!
真是可悲
It's sad, really.
我本以为我把你变得更好
I thought I made you better.
没想到你却让人失望
Turns out, you're quite the disappointment.
呀！
Yaah!
我猜我只不过是你另一个失败品而已
I guess I'm another one of your failures,
就像你制造混血最终失败一样
like how you failed at making hybrids,
就像你让你的家人失望一样
how you failed your family.
现在看起来你甚至可能
Now it looks like you're even
要让你自己的孩子失望了
gonna fail your own kid.
那就这样终结你乏味又渺小的一生吧
And thus ends your tedious, little life.
至少它不会耗时太久
At least it was brief.
呀！啊！！
Yaagh! Ugh...
杀了我吧
Do it.
你永远不会毁掉我的
You're never gonna break me.
你唯一能做的就是杀了我
Only thing you could do is kill me.
来吧  杀了我  让一切都结束
So go on. Go on. Get it over with.
啊…
Ah...
你想让我结束你的痛苦  是吗？
You want me to end your suffering, don't you?
嗯？我确实毁掉了你  夺走了你的一切
Hmm? I did break you, took everything from you,
而现在你又祈求我结束你那
and now you're begging me to sweep away the shards
破碎渺小的生命
of your shattered, little life.
让你死就太便宜你了
Death offers more peace than you deserve.
更好的方式是让你生不如死
It's better to let you live,
每个清晨你醒来就会意识到
and each morning, you will wake knowing
你这样卑微的活着
that your wretched existence continues
仅仅是由于我的施舍
only by my will.
现在你走吧  去享受你剩下的日子吧
Now go and live the rest of your days
你要知道你对我来说什么都不是
knowing you are nothing to me.
你知道曾经有多少傻子试图要
Do you know how many fools have tried
战胜我哥哥么?
to vanquish my brother?
如果你和他对立  他会杀了你
If you stand against him, he will kill you,
那种可怕又血腥的场面
and it will be awful and bloody,
我绝对不会旁观的
and I will not stand around and watch.
你忘了我有一个秘密武器…Davina
You forget I have a secret weapon... Davina,
是几个世纪以来最厉害的女巫
the most powerful witch in the last couple centuries.
如果她能找出杀掉你哥哥的办法呢？
What if she can find a way to kill him?
你什么都不知道 是吗？
You don't know, do you?
你杀了Klaus的话
You can't kill Klaus,
自己也会跟着死
not without dying yourself.
从我哥哥Kol和Finn的死亡中
We learned it from the deaths
我们知道了一些事情
of my brothers Kol and Finn.
如果一个始祖吸血鬼死了
If an Original dies, every vampire
那他们这条血脉的吸血鬼都会跟着死去
ever made from their line dies with him.
即使你杀死了Klaus 他也终将是赢家
Even if you kill Klaus, he'll still win.
一千年来都是这样
It's been that way for 1,000 years.
那就是他的诀窍  他永远都是赢家
That's his trick. He always wins.
还有一个方法
There's another way.
什么方法？
What would that be?
我们把他永远的埋在这里
We bury him down here forever.
你疯了吗？
Are you mad?
这地方也许能埋得了你那帮乌合之众
This little chamber of horrors may work
但是你真的认为
for your riffraff, but do you really think
这能困得住我哥哥吗？
it will hold my brother?
难道不值得冒这个险吗？你知道我是正确的
Isn't it worth the risk? You know I'm right.
Klaus永远都不会停止对你的控制
Klaus will never stop trying to control you.
难道我真应该相信
And I'm supposed to believe
一个世纪以后  你会突然愿意
that after a century, suddenly you're willing
愿意冒生命危险挣脱他的束缚跟我在一起？
to risk death at his hands to be with me?
我想保护我的家园
I want to defend my home.
我想要自由 如果这意味着
I want to be free, and if that means
我还可以跟你在一起
I get to be with you,
这些都是我要埋葬他的更为正当的理由
all the more reason to bury him.
现在告诉我  你想要什么？
Now you tell me, what do you want?
你们在这啊
There you are.
原来你找到了我们的漫游侠
I see you found our wandering stray.
也许她能解开
Perhaps she could shed some light
当下的疑惑
on the situation.
这…
This...
似乎是个混血的尸体
Would appear to be the body of a hybrid.
他的名字叫Dwayne
His name was Dwayne.
不管他是谁  我反正没让他认祖归宗
Well, whoever he was, I didn't sire him.
知道这是怎么回事么？
Any idea how that's possible?
说的好像你真不知道一样
As if you didn't know.
啊呀呀…
Ah...
你们俩真是自来熟吗？
Aren't you two fast friends?
好吧  快说
Well, come on, then.
你们在背后合谋出了什么点子
What horrible accusation have you conspired
来对抗我呢？
to levy against me?
Tyler Lockwood 带Hayley来这证实一个理论
Tyler Lockwood brought Hayley here to test a theory,
她孩子的血液可以让混血认祖归宗
that the blood of her child could be used to sire hybrids.
他宣称你知道这件事
He claims you knew that.
而且  你原打算
Furthermore, you intended
利用这一点来建造一支军队
to use this knowledge to build an army.
显然  你认为这件事是真的
And, of course, you assume it's true.
我的意思是  还有什么能让我这种人
I mean, why else would I show
对自己的亲生骨肉感兴趣呢？
any interest in my own flesh and blood?
一个心碎的 爱哭的小屁孩
A heartbroken, little crybaby
来指控我 而我的亲哥哥
points his finger at me, and my own brother
居然受骗上当 宁愿去相信他说的
falls in line, eager to believe it.
你往坏处想得可真快啊
How quickly you assume the worst,
尤其跟她有关的时候
especially when it comes from her.
哦 别义愤填膺了
Oh, spare me your indignation.
你什么时候表现出来哪怕一点
When have you ever demonstrated any kind of concern
对Hayley和孩子的关心呢？
towards Hayley or her child
除了你自私自利的追求以外
beyond your own selfish pursuits,
还有 你最开始是怎么对我说的？
and what was it you once said to me?
每位国王都需要一个继承人
"Every King needs an heir."
我的大哥
My big brother,
所以你怀疑我的意图咯
so you doubt my intentions.
我不能说我惊讶我不能说我惊讶
Well, I can't say I'm surprised.
在高尚的Elijah身旁
Standing beside the noble Elijah,
我只能是个微不足道的弟弟
how can I be anything but the lesser brother...
一个骗子 一个操纵者
a liar, a manipulator,
或是个私生子
a bastard?
在你眼中我就是这样的人 对吧
That's all I am to you, isn't it,
对Rebekah来说也是 而且
and to Rebekah, and judging
从Hayley对你言听计从来看
by the way Hayley hangs on your every word,
很明显她也是这么想的
it's clear she feels the same way.
毫无疑问 我的孩子也会一样
No doubt, my child will, as well.
弟弟 如果我...
Brother, if I...
该说的我们都说过了
we've said all that needs to be said,
哥哥
brother.
我现在要去扮演你们赋予我的角色了
I'll play the role I've been given.
啊！ Klaus！
Agh!Klaus!
哦...
Oh...
你俩好好享受彼此的陪伴吧
You two enjoy each other's company.
一旦幻觉出现 失去理智
You'll have much to bond over
你们将难分彼此
once the hallucinations and dementia set in.
就把我刚才咬的那一口
Consider that bite
当作送给你俩的分别之礼吧
my parting gift to you both.
哦...
Oh...
可以了
That's it.
你自由了
You're free.
啊...
Uh...
没错 我能感觉到
You're right. I can feel it.
之前 我一直在想
Before, I was always thinking
Klaus想让我做什么
about what Klaus would want me to do.
现在我只想 去他的
Now I'm like ,"screw that guy."
哈哈哈！
Ha! Ha ha ha!
Klaus Mikaelson见鬼去吧 哈！
Klaus Mikaelson can suck it. Ha!
怎么了 怎么这副表情？
What? What's that look for?
Marcel希望我能让你忘记我
Marcel wants me to make you forget about me.
哦 你不用非得那么做啊
Oh, well, you don't have to do that.
这条命是我欠你的
I owe you my life.
我会替你保密的
I'll keep your secret.
再说 能再次跟普通人交流
Besides, it's kind of nice
的感觉真棒
just talking to someone normal again.
你觉得我是个普通人？
You think I'm normal?
我是个像怪胎一样隐居在教堂阁楼的
I'm a 16-year-old witch living in a church attic
十六岁女巫
like some kind of freak.
我是个喜欢混俱乐部的男同
I'm a gay club kid who died
然后死掉变成了吸血鬼
and came back as a vampire.
-哈哈 -是啊
Ha ha! Yeah.
普通是相对而言的 对吧？
Normal is kind of relative, you know?
来 我们拉钩
Here. Pinky swear on it.
你不一定非得帮我
You don't have to help.
我可以自己从狼人古董里找到
I can dig through the werewolf antique show
想要的东西
on my own.
另外 你是不是应该往伤口上
Besides, shouldn't you put some kind
涂点药膏什么的？
of ointment or something on that?
一个咬伤而已 我死不了的
The bite won't kill me.
就像Niklaus他自己 就是一个麻烦而已
Like Niklaus himself, it's more of a nuisance